Adefeso Qudus (Frontend Developer)

With 5 years of experience in frontend development, I have worked with a range of modern frontend frameworks and technologies (React, Nextjs, Svelte, React Native) to build intuitive and engaging user interfaces. I've been involved in projects that implement best practices like Micro-Frontend Architecture, UI Component Libraries, and UX Design Systems.

| \square | adefesog | @ama | il.com |
|-----------|----------|----------|--------|
| | aacicoca | (W GIIIG | |

+2348168127242

ĬM LinkedIn

Github

Portfolio

Education

Moshood Abiola Polytechnic

Higher Nationa Diploma in Electrical/ Electronics Engineering

Skills

JavaScript

TypeScript

React

Nextjs

React Native

Tailwindcss,

Git/Github

Redux/Redux Toolkit

React Query

REST & GraphQL APIs

HTML5

CSS

Interests

Running/Jogging

Reading

Experience

Lead Frontend Developer - FunZ

May 2024 - Present

- Leading the development of an event management platform
- Achieved over 25,000 registered users and 200K+ visits since the platform's launch.
- Implemented event analytics tools to enable event organizers to visualize and track sales performance effectively.
- Spearheaded an international feature allowing global event hosting with multi-currency payment options for seamless transactions.
- Implementing custom event tracking in Google Analytics 4 to measure user engagement and conversion rates.

Frontend Developer - CluxMedia

September 2023 - May 2024

- Worked on an AI platform at to assist doctors in generating comprehensive H&P notes and assessments.
- Enabled the platform to process inputs such as chief complaints, key patient history, and suggested diagnoses.
- Automated the creation of detailed H&P notes, assessments, and clinical plans, streamlining patient care and decision-making.

Frontend Developer - Ecscorp Resources

July 2022 - August 2023 | Nigeria

- Worked on the migration of an e-commerce codebase from React
 16 to React 18, managing code refactoring & dependency updates.
- Worked on the headless integration with Magento to enable seamless inventory, cart, and order management.
- Worked on the implementation of robust internationalization features to support multiple languages and regions.

Frontend Developer - The Creative Ally

March 2021 - May 2022 | Nigeria

- Collaborated with the team to develop a platform connecting students with potential employers.
- Worked closely with UI/UX designer to build beautiful and usable user interface